Malique Lovence

■ Maliquelovence@hotmail.com 🔲 4707536488 🛅 https://www.linkedin.com/in/malique-lovence-6023a0132/ 🛥 https://malz414.github.io/porto/

SUMMARY

Games programming graduate with a background in C++, HTML, CSS, Javascript, and MySQL. Experience working freelance as a web developer. Highly analytical, motivated and skilled at solving programming problems. Can work well both independently and in a team.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic designer

Antigua Charter Yacht Show

November 2023 - December 2023, Antigua

• Designed and created, marketing materials, and digital media campaigns with up to date techniques and principles of design that adhere to the organization's brand identity. • Collaborated with cross-functional teams to develop and execute on-time and projects and initiatives. • Utilized Photoshop, and Canva to create logos, digital graphics, and web, print and social media layouts, resulting in a 30% improvement in client engagement.

Full Stack Developer

Freelance

November 2022 - July 2023, Antigua

• Engineered high-impact websites using Wordpress and HTML5/CSS, resulting in a 30% increase in brand awareness.• Applied Javascript and PHP to develop sophisticated backend features, facilitating digital engagement for hundreds of customers.• Developed software using C++ to streamline data input, effectively doubling efficiency.• Employed various editing software to craft compelling videos and images tailored to enhance brand identity.

Marketing Intern

WeBeStitching

February 2018 - August 2019, Antigua

• Spearheaded the creation and maintenance of an impactful online presence, showcasing products and services to potential customers. • Orchestrated marketing initiatives, including dynamic social media campaigns, contributing to a 10% increase in company visibility and sales. • Designed and digitized logos, enabling brands to present their optimal image.

PROJECTS

Mystic Cabin Defence

 $\textit{Game Jam} \cdot \textit{https://malz414.itch.io/arcane-chronicles} \cdot \textit{September 2023 - October 2023}$

• This project was created to be entered into a game jam, winning prizes through user voting. • Reprogrammed the Unity asset PDollar Point-Cloud Gesture Recognizer, enabling spell instantiation based on player-drawn shapes. • Animated 2D sprites using Photoshop for in-game enemies, each with their own mechanics. • Implemented a user-friendly UI to monitor player score, health, and settings adjustments.

CarniVRal

University • https://malz414.github.io/porto/projects.html • February 2022 - July 2022

• This project created for my university final, is now being used as an example of remarkable work achieving a grade of 84%.• Leveraged XR manager to craft an immersive VR space with interactables and games.• Contributed to 80% of model creation, including carnival stalls and other elements.• Recorded and edited sound effects for a seamless user experience.

Graphics Program

University • https://malz414.github.io/porto/projects.html • February 2022 – June 2022

• Developed a graphics program for texture mapping, incorporating parallax and normal mapping.• Implemented features such as random terrain generation, tessellation, and fog.• Integrated post-processing effects including blur and bloom for enhanced visuals.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Games Programming

DeMontfort University · Leicester, UK · 3.7

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, PHP, C++, C#, LUA, OpenGL, MySQLAdobe Photoshop, Wordpress, Git, Unity,